Luther-Bagby collection, Inclusive: 1821-2001, Bulk: 1890-1970
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Scrapbooks, 1877-1971; 6; 5 document boxes and three boxes of oversized materials.
  - English Speaking Club Subject Files and Photographs: (3 of 4), 1949-1955 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - English Speaking Club Subject Files and Photographs: (4 of 4), 1949-1955 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - General, 1901; 1951-1961 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - John Hill Luther Religious Topics, 1899 (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - People and Places in Brazil, undated (Box 124 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Churches and Schools in Brazil, 1898-1927 (Box 125 OVZ, Folder 1)